onlinemoneyclub.co.uk 2019-04-11

# Privacy Policy | Online Money Club

### David Henry & onlinemoneyclub.co.uk privacy policy compliant with GDPR

### Updated 24th May 2018

This privacy policy sets out how David Henry uses and protects any information that you give David Henry when you use this website.

David Henry is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement.

David Henry may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from May 25th 2018

### Your legal rights

Under data protection laws you have rights in relation to your personal data that include the right to request access, correction, erasure, restriction, transfer, to object to processing, to portability of data and (where the lawful ground of processing is consent) to withdraw consent.

If you wish to exercise any of the rights set out above, please email me at david@plrprofitsclub.com or [open a support ticket here](https://davidjen.supportsystem.com/)

You will not have to pay a fee to access your personal data (or to exercise any of the other rights).

However, I may charge a reasonable fee if your request is clearly unfounded, repetitive or excessive or refuse to comply with your request in these circumstances.

When accessing the http://onlinemoneyclub.co.uk  website, we will learn certain information about you during your visit.

Similar to other commercial websites, our website utilizes a standard technology called “cookies” (see explanation below) and server logs to collect information about how our site is used. Information gathered through cookies and server logs may include the date and time of visits, the pages viewed, time spent at our site, and the websites visited just before and just after our own, as well as your IP address.

**Use of Cookies**

A cookie is a very small text document, which often includes an anonymous unique identifier. When you visit a website, that sits computer asks your computer for permission to store this file in a part of your hard drive specifically designated for cookies. Each website can send its own cookie to your browser if your browser’s preferences allow it, but (to protect your privacy) your browser only permits a website to access the cookies it has already sent to you, not the cookies sent to you by other sites.

**Cookie Policy**

**What’s a cookie?**

A “cookie” is a piece of information that is stored on your computer’s hard drive and which records how you move your way around a website so that, when you revisit that website, it can present tailored options based on the information stored about your last visit. Cookies can also be used to analyse traffic and for advertising and marketing purposes.

Cookies are used by nearly all websites and do not harm your system.

If you want to check or change what types of cookies you accept, this can usually be altered within your browser settings. You can block cookies at any time by activating the setting on your browser that allows you to refuse the setting of all or some cookies. However, if you use your browser settings to block all cookies (including essential cookies) you may not be able to access all or parts of my websites.

**How do I use cookies?**

I use cookies to track your use of my website. This enables me to understand how you use the site and track any patterns with regards how you are using my website. This helps me to develop and improve my website as well as products and / or services in response to what you might need or want.

**Cookies are either:**

Session cookies: these are only stored on your computer during your web session and are automatically deleted when you close your browser – they usually store an anonymous session ID allowing you to browse a website without having to log in to each page but they do not collect any personal data from your computer; or

Persistent cookies: a persistent cookie is stored as a file on your computer and it remains there when you close your web browser. The cookie can be read by the website that created it when you visit that website again.  I use persistent cookies sometimes when using platforms such as Google Analytics and Clickfunnels.

**Cookies can also be categorised as follows:**

Strictly necessary cookies: These cookies are essential to enable you to use the website effectively, such as when buying a product and / or service, and therefore cannot be turned off. Without these cookies, the services available to you on my website cannot be provided. These cookies do not gather information about you that could be used for marketing or remembering where you have been on the internet.

Performance cookies: These cookies enable me to monitor and improve the performance of my websites. For example, they allow me to count visits, identify traffic sources and see which parts of the site are most popular.

Functionality cookies: These cookies allow my website to remember choices you make and provide enhanced features. For instance, I may be able to provide you with news or updates relevant to the services you use. They may also be used to provide services you have requested such as viewing a video or commenting on a blog. The information these cookies collect is usually anonymised.

**IP Addresses**

IP addresses are used by your computer every time you are connected to the Internet. Your IP address is a number that is used by computers on the network to identify your computer. IP addresses are automatically collected by our web server as part of demographic and profile data known as “traffic data” so that data (such as the Web pages you request) can be sent to you.

**What data do we collect about you?**

Personal data means any information capable of identifying an individual. It does not include anonymised data.

We may process certain types of personal data about you as follows:

Identity Data may include your first name, maiden name, last name, username, marital status, title, date of birth and gender.

Contact Data may include your billing address, delivery address, email address and telephone numbers.

Financial Data may include your bank account and payment card details.

Transaction Data may include details about payments between us and other details of purchases made by you.

Technical Data may include your login data, internet protocol addresses, browser type and version, browser plug-in types and versions, time zone setting and location, operating system and platform and other technology on the devices you use to access this site.

Profile Data may include your username and password, purchases or orders, your interests, preferences, feedback and survey responses.

Usage Data may include information about how you use our website, products and services.

Marketing and Communications Data may include your preferences in receiving marketing communications from us and our third parties and your communication preferences.

We may also process Aggregated Data from your personal data, but this data does not reveal your identity and as such is not personal data. An example of this is where we review your Usage Data to work out the percentage of website users using a specific feature of our site.

If we link the Aggregated Data with your personal data so that you can be identified from it, then it is treated as personal data.

**Sensitive Data**

We do not collect any Sensitive Data about you. Sensitive data refers to data that includes details about your race or ethnicity, religious or philosophical beliefs, sex life, sexual orientation, political opinions, trade union membership, information about your health and genetic and biometric data. We do not collect any information about criminal convictions and offences.

Where we are required to collect personal data by law, or under the terms of the contract between us and you do not provide us with that data when requested, we may not be able to perform the contract (for example, to deliver goods or services to you). If you don’t provide us with the requested data, we may have to cancel a product or service you have ordered but if we do, we will notify you at the time.

**How we collect your personal data**

We collect data about you through a variety of different methods including:

Direct interactions: You may provide data by filling in forms on our site (or otherwise) or by communicating with us by post, phone, email or otherwise, including when you:

Order our products or services;

Create an account on our site;

Subscribe to our service or publications;

Request resources or marketing be sent to you;

Join a giveaway event either as a contributor or free member;

Enter a competition, prize draw, promotion or survey;

Give us feedback.

Automated technologies or interactions: As you use our site, we may automatically collect Technical Data about your equipment, browsing actions and usage patterns. We collect this data by using cookies, server logs and similar technologies. We may also receive Technical Data about you if you visit other websites that use our cookies. Please see our cookie policy for further details.

Third parties or publicly available sources: We may receive personal data about you from various third parties and public sources as set out below:

Technical Data from the following parties:

Analytics providers such as Google based outside the EU;

Analytics providers such as Facebook based outside the EU;

Advertising networks [such as [Facebook/Google/Youtube/Instagram/Twitter/Hotjar/Also Re-targeting services provided by these companies] based [inside OR outside] the EU];

Search information providers like Google and Bing based [inside OR outside] the EU].

Contact, Financial and Transaction Data from providers of technical payment and delivery services [such as JVZoo, WarriorPlus, Paypal, Clickbank

Identity and Contact Data from data brokers or aggregators based [inside OR outside] the EU].

Identity and Contact Data from publicly available sources such as Companies House and the Electoral Register based inside the EU.

How we use your personal data

We will only use your personal data when legally permitted. The most common uses of your personal data are:

Where we need to perform the contract between us.

Where it is necessary for our legitimate interests (or those of a third party) and your interests and fundamental rights do not override those interests.

Where we need to comply with a legal or regulatory obligation.

Generally, we do not rely on consent as a legal ground for processing your personal data, other than in relation to sending marketing communications to you via email or text message.

You have the right to withdraw consent to marketing at any time by clicking on our Unsubscribe link at the bottom of every one of our email communications or by [submitting a support ticket by Clicking Here](https://davidjen.supportsystem.com/)

**Purposes for processing your personal data  **

Set out below is a description of the ways we intend to use your personal data and the legal grounds on which we will process such data. We have also explained what our legitimate interests are where relevant.

We may process your personal data for more than one lawful ground, depending on the specific purpose for which we are using your data.

1/ To register you as a new customer

Type of data

(a) Identity, (b) Contact

Lawful basis for processing

(a) Performance of a contract with you (b) Necessary for our legitimate interests to recover debts owed to us

2/ To process and deliver your membership site access and app login

Type of data

(a) Identity

(b) Contact

(c) Financial

(d) Transaction

Lawful basis for processing

(a) Performance of a contract with you (b) Necessary for our legitimate interests to recover debts owed to us

(b) Manage payments, fees and charges

(c) Collect and recover money owed to us

3/ To manage our relationship with you which will include:

Type of data

(a) Identity

(b) Contact

(e) Marketing and Communications

Lawful basis for processing

(a) Notifying you about changes to our terms or privacy policy

(b) Asking you to leave a review or take a survey

(a) Performance of a contract with you

4/ To make suggestions and recommendations to you about goods or services that may be of interest to you

Type of data

(a) Identity

(b) Contact

(c) Technical

(d) Usage

(e) Profile

Lawful basis for processing is necessary for our legitimate interests to develop our products/services and grow our business

**Marketing communications**

You will receive marketing communications from us if you have:

Joined as a free gold level member or as a paid platinum paid member

Requested free information from us; or

if you provided us with your details at the point of entry for us to send you marketing communications;

Joined a giveaway event as a contributor or as a free member hosted by David Henry Marketing or other giveaway hosting companies

and

In each case, you have not opted out of receiving that marketing.

We will get your express opt-in consent before we share your personal data with any third party for marketing purposes.

You can ask us or third parties to stop sending you marketing messages at any time by following the opt-out links on any marketing message sent to you or by submitting a support ticket by Clicking Here at any time.

Where you opt out of receiving our marketing communications, this will not apply to personal data provided to us as a result of a product/service purchase, warranty registration, product/service experience or other transactions.

**Change of purpose  **

We will only use your personal data for the purposes for which we collected it, unless we reasonably consider that we need to use it for another reason and that reason is compatible with the original purpose.

If we need to use your personal data for a purpose unrelated to the purpose for which we collected the data, we will notify you and we will explain the legal ground of processing.

We may process your personal data without your knowledge or consent where this is required or permitted by law.

**Email Information**

If you choose to correspond with us through email, we may retain the content of your email messages together with your email address and our responses. We provide the same protections for these electronic communications that we employ in the maintenance of information received online, mail and telephone. This also applies when you register for our website, sign up through any of our forms using your email address or make a purchase on this site.

**Email Policies**

We are committed to keeping your e-mail address confidential. We do not sell, rent, or lease our subscription lists to third parties, and we will not provide your personal information to any third-party individual, government agency, or company at any time unless strictly compelled to do so by law.

We will use your e-mail address solely to provide timely information about

Product updates and upgrades

General marketing updates and information

Password resets

System issues

System downtime

We will maintain the information you send via e-mail in accordance with applicable federal law.

**CAN-SPAM Compliance**

In compliance with the CAN-SPAM Act, all e-mail sent from our organization will clearly state who the e-mail is from and provide clear information on how to contact the sender. In addition, all e-mail messages will also contain concise information on how to remove yourself from our mailing list so that you receive no further e-mail communication from us.

**Choice/Opt-Out**

Our site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners by reading the unsubscribe instructions located at the bottom of any e-mail they receive from us at any time.

Users who no longer wish to receive our newsletter or promotional materials may opt-out of receiving these communications by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the e-mail.

**Third Party Links**

http://plrprofitsclub.com may contain links to many other websites. We cannot guarantee the accuracy of information found at any linked site. Links to or from external sites not owned or controlled by David Henry Marketing do not constitute an endorsement by or any of its employees of the sponsors of these sites or the products or information presented therein.

Clicking on those links or enabling those connections may allow third parties to collect or share data about you. I do not control these third-party websites and am not responsible for their privacy statements. When you leave my website, I suggest you read the privacy notice of every website you visit.

By accessing this web site, you are agreeing to be bound by these web site Terms and Conditions of Use, all applicable laws and regulations, and agree that you are responsible for compliance with any applicable local laws. If you do not agree with any of these terms, you are prohibited from using or accessing this site. The materials contained in this web site are protected by applicable copyright and trade mark law.

**Intellectual Property Rights**

All copyrights, trademarks, patents and other intellectual property rights in and on our website and all content and software located on the site shall remain the sole property of or its licensors. The use of our trademarks, content and intellectual property is forbidden without the express written consent from.

You must not:

Republish material from our website without prior written consent.

Sell or rent material from our website.

Reproduce, duplicate, create derivative, copy or otherwise exploit material on our website for any purpose.

Redistribute any content from our website, including onto another website.

**Acceptable Use**

You agree to use our website only for lawful purposes, and in a way that does not infringe the rights of, restrict or inhibit anyone else’s use and enjoyment of the website. Prohibited behaviour includes harassing or causing distress or inconvenience to any other user, transmitting obscene or offensive content or disrupting the normal flow of dialogue within our website.

You must not use our website to send unsolicited commercial communications. You must not use the content on our website for any marketing related purpose without our express written consent.

**Restricted Access**

We may in the future need to restrict access to parts (or all) of our website and reserve full rights to do so. If, at any point, we provide you with a username and password for you to access restricted areas of our website, you must ensure that both your username and password are kept confidential.

**Use of Testimonials**

In accordance to with the FTC guidelines concerning the use of endorsements and testimonials in advertising, please be aware of the following:

Testimonials that appear on this site are received via text, audio or video submission. They are individual experiences, reflecting real life experiences of those who have used our products and/or services in some way. They are individual results and results do vary. We do not claim that they are typical results. The testimonials are not necessarily representative of all of those who will use our products and/or services.

The testimonials displayed in any form on this site (text, audio, video or other) are reproduced verbatim, except for correction of grammatical or typing errors. Some may have been shortened. In other words, not the whole message received by the testimonial writer is displayed when it seems too lengthy or not the whole statement seems relevant for the public.

is not responsible for any of the opinions or comments posted on http://inboxingpro.com. is not a forum for testimonials, however provides testimonials as a means for customers to share their experiences with one another. To protect against abuse, all testimonials appear after they have been reviewed by management, but we do not share the opinions, views or commentary of any testimonials on http://inboxingpro.com – the opinions are strictly the views of the testimonial source.

The testimonials are never intended to make claims that our products and/or services can be used to diagnose, treat, cure, mitigate or prevent any disease. Any such claims, implicit or explicit, in any shape or form, have not been clinically tested or evaluated.

How Do We Protect Your Information and Secure Information Transmissions?

Email is not recognized as a secure medium of communication. For this reason, we request that you do not send private information to us by email. However, doing so is allowed, but at your own risk. Some of the information you may enter on our website may be transmitted securely via a secure medium known as Secure Sockets Layer, or SSL. Credit Card information and other sensitive information is never transmitted via email.

We may use software programs to create summary statistics, which are used for such purposes as assessing the number of visitors to the different sections of our site, what information is of most and least interest, determining technical design specifications, and identifying system performance or problem areas.

For site security purposes and to ensure that this service remains available to all users, uses software programs to monitor network traffic to identify unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, or otherwise cause damage.

**Disclaimer and Limitation of Liability**

Makes no representations, warranties, or assurances as to the accuracy, currency or completeness of the content contain on this website or any sites linked to this site.

All the materials on this site are provided “as is” without any express or implied warranty of any kind, including warranties of merchantability, noninfringement of intellectual property or fitness for any purpose. In no event shall or its agents or associates be liable for any damages whatsoever (including, without limitation, damages for loss of profits, business interruption, loss of information, injury or death) arising out of the use of or inability to use the materials, even if has been advised of the possibility of such loss or damages.

**Policy Changes**

We reserve the right to amend this privacy policy at any time with or without notice. However, please be assured that if the privacy policy changes in the future, we will not use the personal information you have submitted to us under this privacy policy in a manner that is materially inconsistent with this privacy policy, without your prior consent.

We are committed to conducting our business in accordance with these principles to ensure that the confidentiality of personal information is protected and maintained.

**Contact**

If you have any questions regarding this policy, or your dealings with our website, please contact us here:

David Henry

5 Spencer Green

Whiston

Rotherham

South Yorkshire

S60 4NR

UK

david@plrprofitsclub.com
